Anita Weschler Papers
Anita Weschler Papers
- Writings
  - Writings of others
    - Fragment, unidentified (Box 83)
Hitzig, William M., Dr. *Feb 3, 1943 [Feb 5, 1943 PM]
Hodes, Alfred Lucein [circa 1930] Nov 8, 1943
Hofmann, Else J. [Mar 13, 1942 PM] Mar 30, 1942 Sep 1, 1942 Sep [?] 1942 Oct 21 [1943 PM] Apr 27, 1944 Jan 14, 1945 Mar 1949
Hollerity, Lucia B. Feb 5, 1935 Feb 23, 1935 Mar 28, 1935 [circa 1940]
Holmes, Frank Graham (1878-1954) Oct 15, 1935 Nov 6, 1935
Hopper, Inslee A. Feb 10, 1936 Apr 21, 1936 *Apr 5, 1938 Apr 6, 1938 May 2, 1938 Aug 29, 1938 Dec 3, 1938 *Dec 8, 1938 *Dec 12, 1938 [circa 1938] *[circa 1938] Jan 3, 1939 *Jan 6, 1939 Jan 11, 1939 *Feb 21, 1939 Feb 27, 1939 Mar 2, 1939 *[circa 1939] *Feb 29 [1940] Mar 4, 1940 Apr 4, 1940 Jan 18, 1941 Feb 11, 1941
Horton, Ruth D. Feb 11, 1937
Houghton-Mifflin Company Feb 8, 1935 Mar 13, 1936
Hudnut, Joseph (1886-1968) Dec 21, 1936 Feb 1, 1937 Mar 30, 1937 [Mar 25, 1939 PM] Apr 18, 1939 *May 3, 1939 May 23, 1939 *Jun 5 [1939] *Aug 17, 1939 *Oct 14, 1939 *[circa 1939] *[circa 1939] Apr 1, 1940 Apr 13, 1940 Apr 30, 1940 PM] May 6, 1940 PM] May 27, 1940 [May ? 1940 PM] *Jun 8, 1940 Jun 11, 1940 PM *Jun 1 1, 1940 Jun 17 [1940 PM] [Jun 21, 1940 PM] [circa Jun 1940] *[Nov ? 1940] *Nov 20 [1940 PM] *Nov 27 [1940 PM] *[Dec 18, 1940 PM] *[Dec 28, 1940 PM] *[circa 1940] Jan 10, 1941 PM Jan 16, 1941 PM Jan 24, 1941 PM *Feb 1, 1941 Feb 1, 1941 *Feb 19, 1941 Feb 19, 1941 Feb 26, 1941 PM [circa Feb? 1941] *Mar 2, 1941 Mar 4, 1941 PM *Mar 5, 1941 Mar 18, 1941 PM Mar 24, 1941 PM Mar 24, 1941 PM Apr 9, 1941 PM Apr 18, 1941 PM [circa Apr ? 1941] May 13, 1941 PM May 15, 1941 PM May 21, 1941 PM May 22, 1941 PM Jun 6, 1941 PM Jun 26, 1941 PM Jul 1, 1941 PM Jul 11, 1941 PM Jul 23 [1941 PM] Aug 24, 1941 Dec 23, 1941 PM *[Dec ? 1941] *[circa 1941] Jun 12 [1943 PM] Sep 27, 1943 PM *Oct 5, 1943 Oct 21 [1943 PM] Nov 23, 1943 PM [circa Nov 23, 1943 PM] Dec 31, 1943 PM [Jan 10, 1944 PM] *Jan 16, 1944 [Jan 24, 1944 PM] [Feb 7, 1944 PM] *[circa Feb 15, 1944] [Feb 21, 1944 PM] [Mar 17, 1944 PM] [Apr 4, 1944 PM] [Apr 6, 1944 PM] [Apr 20, 1944 PM] *May 13, 1944 [May 13, 1944 PM] [May 29, 1944 PM] [Jun 6, 1944 PM] [Jun 10, 1944 PM] [Jun 28, 1944 PM] [Jul 10, 1944 PM] [Jul 29, 1944 PM] [Sep 10, 1944 PM] [Sep 20, 1944 PM] [Sep 30, 1944 PM] [Sep 30, 1944 PM] [Oct 3, 1944 PM] [Oct 16, 1944 PM] [Nov 4, 1944 PM] [Nov 9, 1944 PM] [Dec 8, 1944 PM] [Dec 28, 1944 PM] Feb 20, 1945 Mar 30, 1945 PM] [Apr 14, 1945 PM] [Apr 26, 1945 PM] [May 14, 1945 PM] [Jun 8, 1945 PM] [Aug 1, 1945 PM] Sep 25 [1945 PM] [Oct 17, 1945 PM] Jun 10, 1946 Jul 26, 1946 Sep 14 [1946 PM] Jan 2, 1947 [Jan 16, 1947 PM] Feb 20, 1947 Apr 9 [1947 PM] [May 3, 1947 PM] Oct 15, 1948 Oct 16, 1948 Oct 27, 1948 Nov 18, 1948 [Dec 18, 1948 PM] Feb 9, 1949 Apr 18, 1949 Jun 20, 1949 Jul 25, 1949 Jul 31, 1949 [Dec 31, 1949 PM] Jan 7, 1950 Jan 30, 1950 [Feb 13, 1950 PM] [Feb 24, 1950 PM] [Mar 5, 1950 PM] [Mar 16, 1950 PM] Mar 31, 1950 Jun 26, 1950 Sep 27, 1950 Dec 13, 1950 [Jan 22, 1951 PM] [Jan 25, 1951 PM] [Dec 23, 1951 PM] [Jan 16, 1952 PM] Feb 13, 1952 Dec 31, 1952 [Jan 30, 1953 PM] Feb 16, 1953 Jul 23, 1953 Oct 1, 1953 Oct 15, 1953 Jan 5, 1954 *[Oct 13, 1955] Oct 22, 1955 [Dec.23, 1955 PM] Jan 9, 1956 Jan 4, 1957 n.d. n.d. n.d.
Huguenin, Eloise Parkhurst Feb 16, 1937
Humphrey, Doris (1895-1958) [Jul 13, 1933 PM] May 2, 1939 PM Oct 12, 1944 [Dec 31, 1946 PM] [circa 1946] Dec 18, 1956 Dec 1957 Dec 1958
Hunn, Marianne Jul 14, 1952 [Jul 23, 1952 PM] Sep 15, 1952 Sep 22, 1952 Oct 1 [1952 PM] Oct 23 [1952 PM] Nov 3 [circa 1952] [Nov 13, 1952 PM] [Dec 4, 1952 PM] [Dec 8, 1952 PM] Dec 9, 1952 [Dec 15, 1952 PM] Dec 19, 1952 Dec 29, 1952 [circa 1952]
Hunterdon County Art Center [circa 1955) Mar 26 [1957 PM] Apr 8, 1957 Apr 1958
Hutchens, John K. *Apr 28, 1948
Hutchison, Howard B. Jan 15, 1947 May 7, 1947 Jun 13, 1947 Aug 20, 1950
James, Jesse H. Jr. May 28, 1941 PM Jul 3, 1941 PM Aug 19, 1941 PM Sep 11, 1941 PM Sep 20, 1941 PM Sep 23, 1941 PM Dec 21, 1941 Jan 6, 1942 PM
Jaworski, J.A.C. *Apr 26, 1943
Jenni, Donald Jan 4, 1957 Jul 8 [1957 PM] Jun 25 [1958 PM] Jul 19 [1958 PM] [Aug 1, 1958 PM] [Aug 4, 1958 PM] May 31, 1960 Jul 1, 1960 *[circa Jul ? 1960]
Jerrard, Elise Feb 9, 1937
Jewell, Edward Alden (1888-1947) *Mar 27, 1947 Apr 4, 1947
John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation *Oct 14, 1939 [Feb ? 1940] Feb 10, 1940
Jonas, Louis Paul (1894- ) Oct 20, 1946 Apr 8, 1947 [Nov 24, 1947 PM] Nov 28, 1947 [Oct 26, 1948 PM] [Sep 8, 1949 PM] [Jan 1, 1950 Mar 1950 [Jul 10, 1950 PM] [Sep 24, 1950 PM] Jan 1, 1951 Oct 23, 1952 Jan 11, 1955 [Oct 23, 1959 PM] n.d.
Juster Gallery Oct 22, 1957
Kane, Margeret Brassier (1909- ) Nov 11, 1950 Dec 16, 1950
Kallock, Almansor Jan 4, 1928 Dec 25, 1929 Nov 25, 1930 Dec 17, 1930 Nov 6, 1931 Dec 25, 1931 Feb 19, 1932 Mar 18, 1932 Mar 29, 1932 Apr 2, 1932 Nov 30, 1932 Mar 14, 1932 Mar 14, 1932 Apr 11, 1938 Jan 15, 1941
Katzenberg, Elva S. *Feb 6, 1937 [Feb 11, 1937 PM] [Feb 24, 1937 PM] Mar 2, 1937 [Apr 19, 1937 PM] Apr 27, 1937 10, 1937 May 26 [1937 PM] Jun 7 [circa 1937] Jun 7 [1937 PM] Jun 27, 1937 [Dec 14, 1937 PM] Dec 19, 1937 Dec 29 [1937] [1937 PM] [circa 1937] Feb 5, [1938] Mar 14, 1939
Kendall, Beatrice Feb 12, 1937
Kent, Fay Barnaby Feb 17, 1937
Klonis, Stewart (1901- ) [Aug 14, 1957 PM]
Koestler, Elsa Weschler Jul 8, 1924 Jul 1, 1925 Jul 13, 1925 Jul 18 [circa 1925] Aug 6, 1925 [Aug 7, 1925 PM] Dec 10, 1927 Feb 25, 1928 Apr 12, 1928 Apr 18, 1928 Apr 23 [1928] Apr 26 [1928] Apr 28 [1928] Apr 28 [1928 PM] May 19 [1928] May 22 [1928 PM] Jul 7 [1928 PM] Jul 15, 1928 Aug 9, 1928 Aug 16, 1928 Aug 30 [circa 1928] [Sep 12, 1928 PM] Sep 12, 1928 Sep 13, 1928 Feb 14, 1929 Apr 23 [1929 PM] Dec 9, 1929 [circa 1929] Jan 12, 1930 May 25, 1930 Jun 16 [1930 PM] [Aug 20, 1930 PM] Nov 12, 1930 Jul 22, 1932 [Aug 25 1933 PM] Dec 26 (1933 PM] Jun 15, 1934 Jul 14 [1934 PM] [Aug 23, 1934 PM] [Jun 23, 1935 PM] Jul 14, 1935 Aug 21 [1935 PM] Sep 18, 1935 Jul 21, 1936 [1936 PM] Apr 6 [1937 PM] [Aug 20, 1937 PM] Jan 5, 1939 Jan 20, 1939 [May 19, 1939 PM] [Jan 12, 1940 PM] [May 24, 1940 PM] Jun 7 [1940 PM] Jun 27 [1940 PM] Jul 8, 1940 Sep 15, 1940 Jan 5 [1941 PM] May 19, 1941 Jul 30, 1941 Aug 22 [1941 PM] Apr 13, 1942 Jul 13, 1942 PM Sep 28, 1942 Nov 4 [1942 PM] Nov 17 [1942 PM] Nov 23, 1942 [circa 1942] Aug 9 [1943 PM] Aug 15, 1943 Jun 29, 1944 Jul 22, 1944 Jan 10, 1945 Mar 26, 1945 Oct 23, 1945 Oct 25, 1945 Mar 4, 1946 Apr 10 [1946 PM] May 7, 1946 Jul 23, 1946 [Oct 14, 1946 PM] [Oct 16, 1946 PM] [Mar 4, 1947 PM] Jun 23, 1947 Jul 14, 1947 Jul 15 147 Aug 30 [circa 1947] [Mar 5, 1948 PM] Jul 27, 1948 [1948] Nov 3, 1949 Mar 19, 1950 Apr 20, 1950 May 24, 1950 [1950 PM] May 25, 1951 Aug 15, 1951 Aug 20, 1951 Sep 15, 1951 Oct 11, 1951 *Dec 1, 1951 Feb 14, 1952 Jul 13, 1952 Aug 25 [1952 PM] [May 27, 1953 PM] Aug 3, 1953 *Mar 14, 1954 May 27, 1954 Aug 10, 1954 Dec 17, 1954 Jan 31, 1955 [circa 1955] Mar 4, 1956 [Mar 12, 1956 PM] Jun 14, 1956 Jul 2, 1956 Jul 9, 1956 Jul 16, 1956 Aug 9, 1956 [circa 1956] [1957 PM] Nov 30, 1959 Dec 13, 1959 Mar 23, 1960 Apr 10, 1960 [circa 1960] n.d.
Korff, Betty Hurd [Nov 11, 1946 PM] Apr 14 [1947 PM] [May 28, 1947 PM] [Jul 25, 1947 PM] Sep 28, [1947 PM] [Apr 9, 1948 PM] Jun 5, 1948 Jun 22 [1948 PM] Aug 6, 1948 Aug 29, 1948 [Nov 16, 1948 PM] [J? 23, 1948 PM] Feb 18 [1949 PM] Feb 20, 1949 Mar 3, 1949 Mar 10, 1949 Apr 23, 1949 Apr 30, 1949 Jul 15[1949] PM] Aug 8, 1949 Sep 1 [1949 PM] [Oct 13, 1949 PM] [Feb 1, 1950 PM] [Mar 5, 1950 PM] Apr 17 [1950 PM] [Aug 10, 1950 PM] Oct 13 11950 PM] Nov 8 [1950 PM] Mar 16 [1951 PM] May 25, 1951 [Aug 10, 1951 PM] [Apr 8, 1952 PM] May 27 [1952 PM] Jul 12 [1952 PM] Aug 22 [1952 PM] [Nov 26, 1952 PM] [Jan 2, 1953 PM] Jun 15 [1953 PM] Jul 21, 1953 Sep 4 [1953 PM] [Jan 21, 1954 PM] Jul 12, 1954 Aug 4, 1954 Aug 8, 1955 Sep 3 [circa 1955] [Jan 28, 1956 PM] Aug 7 [circa 1956] [Aug 10, 1956] [Aug 24, 1957 PM] Apr 20, 1959 Aug 26, 1959 [May 28, 1959 PM] n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d. n.d.
Korff, Serger A. (1906- ) [Mar 7, 1950 PM]
Koslow, Julis May 2 [1955 PM] Aug 31 [1955 PM] Nov 18, 1957
Kozlow, Sigmund (1913- ) Jul 12, 1958
Krugar,x Louise (1924- ) Mar 13, 1956
Kubik, Gail T. (1914- ) Jul 29, 1940 Dec 2, 1940 Apr 11, 1943 Nov 9, 1948
Laessle, Albert (1877-1954) Nov 8, 1928 Dec 20, 1934
Lamprey, Louise (1869- ) Dec 12, 1921 Jan 3, 1922 Mar 24, 1922 Dec 18, 1922 Apr 9, 1923 Jul 10, 1923 Jul 15, 1923 Aug 18, 1923 Dec 29, 1923 Mar 23, 1924 Apr 5, 1924 Apr 18, 1924 Apr 22, 1924 Jun 8, 1924 [Dec 19, 1924 PM] Dec 24 [1924] Jul 28, 1927 Nov 12, 1927 Mar 25, 1928 Dec 12, 1928 Jul 19, 1930 Oct 16, 1930 Dec 30, 1930 Mar 18, 1931 Aug 6, 1931 Nov 30, 1932 Apr 20, 1937 Apr 25, 1937 May 6, 1937 May 20, 1940 Jul 18, 1943 Aug 12, 1943 Dec 7, 1943 Jan 19, 1944 Jun 16, 1944 Sep 3 [1944 PM] Apr 21, 1946 Apr 26, 1946 [Sep 20, 1946 PM] Jan 6, 1947 Feb 20, 1947 Sep 28, 1948 n.d.
Langfeld, Beatrice [circa 1922] [Sep 10, 1924 [Sep 25, 1924 PM] [Dec 19, 1924 PM] May 17, 1926 May 28, 1926 Sep 27, 1926 Nov 5 [1926 PM] Jan 15, 1927 Jun 27, 1927 Dec 7, 1927 Apr 8, 1928 [circa 1929] Sep 16 [1930 PM] Nov 26 [1930 PM] Feb 14 [1931 PM] [Nov 12, 1931 PM] May 27 [1931 PM] [circa 1932] n.d. n.d.
Lasku, Edward (1885- ) Jan 5, 1934 Mar 24 [circa 1934]
Laurent, Robert (1890- ) Dec 24, 1950
A. Paul Lefton Company *Dec 21, 1934
Levy, Jeffrey Feb 1937
Lewenthal, Reeves Oct 23, 1944 [Dec 10, 1944] [Mar 3, 1945] [Dec 22, 1945] Feb 2, [1946 PM] Jun 10 [1946 PM] Oct 28 [1946 PM] [1946 PM] *Apr 15, 1948 Apr 17, 1948 Apr 25, 1948 *Jul 4, 1948 Jul 9, 1948 *Sep 1, 1948 *Sep 5, 1948 *Sep 23, 1948 *Oct 17, 1948 Nov 2, 1948 [circa Nov 7, 1948] [Nov 7, 1948 PM]
Lewis, J. Stephen [Feb 4, 1941]
Limon, Jose (1908- ) [Sep 21, 1931 PM] Nov 5, 1931 Jan 21, 1932 [Mar 29, 1932] [Dec 27, 1932 PM] [circa 1932] Nov 5, 1933 [Nov 23, 1933 PM] Nov 20, 1937 Aug 21, 1940 Oct 21, 1940 PM Oct [29 PM] 1940 Oct 30, 1940 Nov 18, 1940 [circa 1940] Jan 6, 1941 Feb [26 PM] 1941 Apr 16, 1941 Aug 1, 1941 Oct 9, 1941 Nov 1941 Jan [?] 1942 Apr 17, 1942 Jun [20 PM] 1942 [circa 1942] [circa 1942] Apr [?] 1943 May 12, 1943 Nov 10, 1943 *Nov 29, 1943 Jan 1944 [circa May 9, 1947] Aug 13, 1951 Jul 6, 1955 [circa 1956] [Nov 8, 1957 PM] n.d. n.d.
Limon, Pauline Lawrence [Aug 14, 1935 PM] [circa 1942] [1944] Jan 29, 1945 Feb 7, 1945 May 7 [1945 PM] Aug 8, 1945 [Jun 28, 1946 PM] Dec 4 [1953 PM] n.d. n.d.
Lipton, Seymour Arthur (1903- ) [Dec 1, 1950 PM]
L.O.F. Glass Fibers Company Jun 21, 1956 Jun 21, 1956 Jun 26, 1956 Jun 27, 1956 Jul 2, 1956 *Jul 21, 1956 Jan 18, 1957
MacDonald, Hazel Christie [circa Feb 1937]
MacDowell, Marian (Mrs. Edward) (1857-1956) *[circa Mar 1934] Mar 18, 1934 Apr 2, 1934 May 5, 1934 Nov 29, 1934 Dec 29, 1934 Jan 16, 1935 Feb 17, 1935 Apr 12, 1935 Apr 25, 1935 May 25, 1935 Oct 6, 1935 Mar 31 [1936 PM] Apr 23 [1936 PM] Sep 18, 1936 Dec 15 [1936 PM] Feb 10, 1937 Feb 26 [1937 PM] Mar 1, 1937 [Mar 26, PM] Apr 4 [1937] May 11, 1937 May 15, 1937 Oct 15 [1937 PM] Oct 28 [1937] Oct 4, 1939 Sep 14, 1940 Feb 15, 1941 May 17, 1941 May 28, 1941 [circa 1943] Nov 25, 1944 Mar 6, 1945 Nov 21, 1947 Feb 2, 1948 Mar 5, 1948 Mar 31, 1948 Apr 24, 1949 Jun 10, 1949 Apr 6, 1950 Jul 31, 1950 Aug 27, 1950 Sep 30, 1950 Jun 10, 1951 Jan 4, 1952 Aug 21, 1952 Nov 14, 1952 Dec 19, 1952 Feb 26, 1953 Jul 21, 1953 Jan 4, 1954 Nov 27, 1954 Dec 13, 1955
MacMillan Company Dec 10, 1945 Dec 28, 1945
Malone, Patrick T. Jun 22, 1951
Manship, Paul (1885- ) Jan 23, 1958
Marceau, Henri (1896- ) Feb 6, 1940 *Mar 14, 1940 [Mar 25, 1940 PM] Apr 16, 1940 *May 3 [1940 PM] Oct 9, 1940 *Oct 25 [1940 PM] *Nov 1, 1940 Nov 6, 1940 *Nov 7, 1940 *Nov 11, 1940 *Nov 28, 1940 Dec 2, 1940 Dec 23, 1940 *[circa 1940] *[circa 1940] Jul 8, 1947 [Feb 7, 1949 PM] Mar 9, 1949 Jul 15, 1949 Jan 16, 1951 Apr 22, 1954 *[Nov 12, 1957
Martin, Dahris [May 2, 1939 PM]
Marx, Burle Jan 24, 1952 Jan 3, 1955 Jun 16, 1957 Apr 19, 1959
Marx, Fannie Mar 27, 1947 Nov 26, 1947 Mar 12, 1948 Jun 28, 1950 Sep 13, 1952
Maxime Oct 3, 1950 May 5, 1950 May 30, 1950 Jun 6, 1950 Jul 10, 1950 Aug 8, 1950 Jan 23, 1951 Jan 9, 1952 Jan 27, 1954 [Dec 24, 1954 PM] [Jan 20, 1956 PM]
Mayer, Sophie Jul 8, 1928 [circa 1929] Feb 4 [1932 PM] [Jul 11, 1932 PM] [Dec 7, 1932 PM] Dec 8 [1934 PM] Mar 9 [circa 1935] May 14 [1935 PM] [Aug 20, 1935 PM] [Nov 4, 1935 PM] [Nov 15, 1935 PM] Dec 7 [1935 PM] [Dec 23, 1935 PM] Jul 1 [1936 PM] May 31 [1937] [Aug 4, 1938 PM] Dec 12, 1939 [Dec 16, 1939 PM] Jan 1 [1940 PM] [Jan 13, 1940 PM] Feb 17 [1941 PM] Nov 19 [1943 PM][1943 PM] Mar 3, 1944 n.d. n.d.
McNickle, D'arcy Sep 4 [1937 PM] [Sep 6, 1937 PM] [Sep 8, 1937 PM] [Sep 12, 1937 PM] [Sep 14, 1937 PM] [Sep 14, 1937 PM] Sep 15 [1937 PM] Sep 16 [1937] [Sep 17, 1937] Sep 19 [1937] Sep 20 [1937 PM] [Sep 22, 1937 PM] Sep 24, 1937 PM. Sep 24, 1937 PM Sep 27, 1937 PM Sep 28, 1937 PM Oct 1, 1937 Oct 1, 1937 Oct 2, 1937 Oct 4, 1937 PM Oct 7, 1937 PM Oct 8, 1937 PM Oct 13, 1937 PM Oct 13, 1937 PM [Oct 16, 1937 PM] [Oct 17, 1937 PM] Oct 20, 1937 PM Oct 25, 1937 Oct 26, 1937 PM Oct 27, 1937 PM Oct 29, 1937 PM [circa Oct 19 7] Nov 2 [ 1937 Nov 3 [1937] Nov 4 [1937] Nov 9 [1937 PM] Nov 15 [1937 PM] Nov 23 [1937] Nov 29 [1937] Dec 1 [1937] Dec 4 [1937 PM] Dec 9 [1937 PM] Dec 13 [1937] Dec 20 [1937 PM] Dec 28 [1937 PM] [circa 1937] Jan 6, 1938 Jan 10, 1938 Jan 11, 1938 Jan 19, 1938 Jan 24, 1938 Jan 26, 1938 Jan 31 [1938 PM] Feb 1 [1938 PM] Feb 3 [1938 PM] Feb 8 [1938 PM] Feb 12 [1938 PM] Feb 18 [1938 PM] Feb 24 [1938 PM] Feb 25 [1938 PM] Feb 26 [1938 PM] Mar 3 [1938 PM] Mar 8 [1938 PM] Mar 9 [1938 PM] Mar 14 [1938 PM] Mar 15 [1938 PM] Mar 18 [1938 PM] Mar 25 [1938 PM] Mar 29 [1938 PM] Apr 2, 1938 Apr 5 [1938] May 16 [1938] Sep 10, 1938 May 16, 1940 Jan 22, 1943 Jan 28, 1943
Metropolitan Museum of Art Oct 28, 1942 May 8, 1945 Mar 1950 May 1950 Jan 10, 1951 Oct 2, 1951 Oct 22, 1952 *[circa Jan 1952] Feb 20, 1952 May 18, 1954 Nov 2, 1957
Miami Beach Public Library & Art Center *Oct 2, 1953 Oct 9, 1953 Oct 9, 1953 *Jan 28, 1954 *Jan 29, 1954 Jan 29, 1954 Feb 4, 1954 [Feb 7, 1954 PM] Feb 22, 1954 Mar 2, 1954
Millu, D. Roy Aug 15, 1931 Nov 4, 1931 Nov 14, 1932
Mitchell, MacNeil, N.Y. State Senator *Feb 25, 1947 Feb 27, 1947
Montague, Ward [Aug 9, 1937 PM] [Aug 14 1937 PM] Aug 21 [1937 PM] Aug 24 [1937 PM] Sep 7 [1937 PM] Sep 17 [1937 PM] Sep 28 [1937 PM] Dec 27, 1937 [Mar 21, 1938 PM] [Aug 16, 1938 PM] [Aug 19, 1938 PM] Feb 2, 1939 Jan 22, 1940 Dec 3 [1940 PM] [circa 1940] Oct 22, 1941 Sep 14, 1942 Jul 11, 1946
Montclair Art Museum Nov 2, 1944 May 29, 1953
Moore, Douglas [circa Feb 1937]
Morehead Planetarium, University of North Carolina Oct 8, 1953 *Oct 15 [1953] Oct 19, 1953 *Feb 24, 1954 Mar 5, 1954 Apr 27, 1954 Jan 22, 1958 *Jan 26, 1958 Mar 29, 1958
Mortimer Levitt Gallery *Apr 23, 1946 Apr 25, 1946 *Aug 2, 1946 [Feb 4, 1947 PM] Jun 18, 1947 Jul 25, 1947 [Sep 5, 1947 PM] Jan 16, 1948 May 23, 1949
Morse, John D. Jun 8, 1945 *Jul 10, 1945
Munson Gallery Mar 30, 1936 Apr 4, 1936 Apr 15, 1936 *Sep 22, 1936
Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute Apr 20, 1958 Sep 8, 1958 Nov 24, 1958
Murphy, Rita Dec 6 [1941 PM)
Museum of Modern Art of New York Nov 29, 1939 Jul 15, 1941 Aug 12, 1942 Sep 2, 1942 Sep 11, 1942 Oct 21, 1942 Nov 12, 1942 Nov 19, 1942 Feb 1, 1943 Feb 1, 1943 *Jun 19, 1946 Jun 27, 1946 *Jul 1, 1946 *Jun 3, 1958 Jun 11, 1958
Museum of Modern Art Gallery, Washington, D.C. Sep 12, 1938 *Sep 14, 1938 Sep 16, 1938 Nov 21, 1938 Nov 8, 1938 Jan 23, 1939
Nathan, Fritz *May 1 [circa 1958] May 3 [1958] *May 12, 1958
National Association of Women Artists, Inc. Apr 25, 1952 [May 17, 1951 PM] Apr 19 [1957] Jan 9, 1958
National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc. Jun 29, 1945 Jul 9, 1945 Jul 18, 1945
National Geographic Society Jan 7, 1942 Aug 22, 1946
National Institute of Arts and Letters Jan 14, 1953 Feb 27, 1953 Dec 17, 1956
National Soap Sculpture Committee May 9, 1941 Jul 26, 1941 Sep 28, 1942 Nov 3, 1943 Jul 2, 1947 Dec 10, 1947 May 11, 1948 Jun 18, 1949 Jul 26, 1949 Sep 28, 1951 Jun 5, 1952 May 19, 1953 Mar 27, 1956
Neff, Emery Feb 20, 1937
New Haven Paint and Clay Club Feb 19, 1936 n.d.
New York Enthusiasts Dec 6, 1948 Dec 20, 1948 Jan 18, 1949 Nov 3, 1949 Nov 28, 1949 [circa Nov 1949] May 29, 1951 Apr 28, 1952 May 28, 1953 Mar 5, 1954 *Mar 8, 1954 Apr 9, 1954 Apr 27, 1954 May 17, 1954 May 24, 1954 Jun 2, 1955 Jun 9, 1955 Dec 13, 1955 May 22, 1956 Dec 17, 1956 Jan 14, 1957 May 1, 1957 May 21, 1957 Mar 25, 1958 Jun 25, 1958 Jul 7, 1958
New York Society of Women Artists Dec 1, 1941
New York Times *Mar 8, 1945 Mar 12, 1945 *Jul 28, 1945
Niedu, George Sep 6, 1938
Nordhousen, A. Henry [Feb 1937] Mar 6, 1937
Nordstrom, Maurice Jan 16, 1956 Mar 7, 1956
Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences Jan 15, 1951 Jun 6, 1951 *Jun 7, 1951 *Jun 21, 1951 *Sep 24, 1953 *Sep 29, 1953 *Oct 9, 1953 *[circa 1953] May 10, 1954 May 25, 1954 *Jun 1, 1954 Jul 14, 1954 *Jul 28, 1954 *Oct 27, 1954 Nov 2, 1954 Mar 22, 1956 n.d. n.d.
Norton, Spenser H. Jan 29, 1938 Nov 12, 1944
Office of War Information Mar 20, 1945
Paeff, Bashka Feb 4, 1937
Patterson, Frances Taylor Feb 15, 1937
Pearce, Glenn [Dec 18, 1929 PM] [Jul 19, 1930 PM] [Sep 22, 1930 PM] [Dec 12, 1930 PM] Dec 13, 1930 Dec 18 [1930 PM] Dec 30, 1930 [Jan 15, 1931 PM] [Feb 1, 1931 PM] [Mar 2, 1931 PM] [circa Mar 5, 1931] [Mar 5, 1931 PM] [Mar 30, 1931 PM] [Apr 24, 1931 PM] [Apr 27, 1931 PM) May 24 [1931 PM] [May 29, 1931 PM] [May ? 1931 PM] [Jun 6, 1931 PM] Jun 19 [1931 PM] Jul 1 [1931 PM] Jul 15 [1931 PM] [Jul 31, 1931 PM] [Aug 15, 1931 PM) [Aug 21, 1931 PM] [Aug 28, 1931 PM] [Sep 1, 1931 PM] [Sep 3, 1931 PM] [Sep 4, 1931 PM] [Sep 9, 1931 PM] [Sep 14, 1931 PM] [Oct 14, 1931 PM] [Oct 20, 1931 PM] [Nov 4, 1931 PM] [Dec 8, 1931 PM] [Dec 15, 1931 PM] [circa 1931] [Mar 15, 1932 PM] [Apr 21, 1932 PM) [Apr 26, 1932 PM] [May 6, 1932 PM] [Jun 7, 1932 PM] [Jul 13, 1932 PM] [Dec 27, 1932 PM] [Feb 28, 1933 PM] [Mar 13, 1933 PM] [Jun 24, 1933 PM] [Oct 18, 1933 PM] [Nov 25, 1933 PM] [Dec 4, 1933 PM] [Dec 20, 1933 PM] [Jan 8, 1934 PM] [Jan 9, 1934 PM] [Jan 11, 1934 PM] [Feb 2, 1934 PM] [Feb 8, 1934 PM] [Feb 15, 1934 PM] [Mar 6, 1934 PM] [Mar 20, 1934 PM] [Apr 16, 1934 PM] [May 11, 1934 PM] [Sep 14, 1934 PM] [Oct 18, 1934 PM] [Dec 1, 1934 PM] [Dec 12, 1934 PM] [Dec 31, 1934 PM] [circa 1934] [circa 1934] [Jan 18, 1935 PM] [Jan 22, 1935 PM] [Jan 24, 1935 PM] [Feb 20, 1935 PM] [Apr 4, 1935 PM] [Apr 24, 1935 PM] Jun 27 [1935 PM] [Aug 10, 1935 PM] Aug 16 [1935 PM] Feb 8 [1936 PM] [Oct 13, 1936 PM] Oct 22 [1936 PM] Oct 26 [1936 PM] Feb 4 [1937 PM] May 27 [1937 PM] [Oct 22, 1937] Jan 22 [1940 PM] *[circa Jan 22, 1940] Apr 15, 1940 Aug 25 [1941 PM] [Dec 3, 1944 PM] [Mar 11, 1945 PM] [Mar 14, 1945 PM] Mar 20, 1945 [Apr 1945] May 20, 1945 [Dec 1946] [circa Dec 1949] [Dec 4, 1951 PM] [Jan 15, 1952 PM] [May 6, 1953 PM] n.d.
Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts Nov 22, 1932 Dec 21, 1948 Dec 21, 1949 Jan 8, 1951 Jan 17, 1951 Feb 1, 1957 [circa Feb 20, 1958] [circa Feb ? 1958] Apr 7 1958 [1959] [circa 1960]
Phelps, William D. Mar 13, 1935
Philadelphia Art Alliance Dec 11, 1950 Apr 2, 1951 Apr 18, 1951 May 29, 1953 Nov 25, 1957
Phillips, Duncan Feb 18, 1935 Dec 27, 1937
Phillips Memorial Gallery (see also Phillips, Duncan) Jul 12, 1940
Piper, Raymond F. (1888-1963) Apr 29, 1949 Jun 28, 1949 Jul 6, 1949 Mar 3, 1950 May 28, 1950 Aug 8, 1950 Apr 19, 1951 Jan 18, 1952 Jan 30, 1952 May 24, 1952 Dec 20, 1952
Poets Magazine Apr 27 [circa 1931] *May 27, 1931 Jun 10, 1931
Pollack, Heinerich May 12, 1928 Jan 30, 1929
Portnow, Henry Mar 4, 1937 May 28, 1937 Jul 29 [1937 PM]
Quirt, Walter [Feb 1937]
Ralph M. Pearson's Design Workshop Dec 2, 1949 Dec 7, 1949 Dec 16, 1949 Dec 21, 1949 Dec 28, 1949 May 6, 1951 May 8, 1951
Raphael & McCord Jun 19, 1939 Jul 7, 1939 *Jul 14 [1939] *Aug 3, 1939 *Aug 18, 1939 *Oct 17, 1939
Raquello, Edward *May 7, 1943 Aug 4, 1943
Raudenbush, George King Feb 9, 1937 Dec 3, 1937
Read, Daniel Feb 20, 1937
Read, Gardner (1913- ) Nov 19, 1937 Feb 6, 1938 Apr 1, 1938 [Aug 1938 PM] [Oct 25, 1938 PM] [Jun 24, 1939 PM] [circa 1939] [Feb 9, 1940 PM] Apr 3, 1941 Nov 23, 1956 n.d.
Read, Vail Jul 25, 1946 [Aug 22, 1946 PM] Aug 24, 1946 Apr 17 [1946 PM] Jul 8, 1946 Jan 15, 1947 Jan 31, 1952
Reader's Digest Dec 9, 1941
Redell, Howard S. Jun 19, 1922 Jul 19, 1922 Aug 29, 1922 [Jun 4, 1924 PM] Jul 16, 1924 [Sep 28, 1928 PM]
Rewald, Estelle [Aug 7, 1953 PM] Jan 30, 1954 Jan 25 [1955 PM] Jul 18 [1955] Jan 31 [1956 PM] [1957] Nov 2, 1958
Reynard, Grant (1887- ) Jan 20, 1937
Rich, Jack *Aug 24, 1945 Aug 25, 1945 Dec 16, 1946
Richardson, Nina Maud May 15, 1936 Jul 29, 1937 Apr 29, 1938 Mar 14, 1939 Mar 12, 1946 May 23, 1946 Jun 28, 1946 Jul 22, 1946 [1946] Jan 7, 1947 Jul 28, 1948 [circa Dec 25, 1957] n.d.
Ringel, Fred J. Sep 4, 1932
Risley, John Nov 12, 1947
Robert M. McBride and Company Jul 24, 1939
Robertson, Priscilla May 29, 1956
Robinson, George S. Apr 4, 1939 Apr 6, 1939 Jul 11, 1939 Jul 11, 1939 Jul 14, 1939 Aug 23, 1939 Sep 19, 1939 Dec 1, 1939 Jan 9, 1940 Jan 24, 1940 Mar 8, 1940 Mar 31, 1943 Apr 14, 1943 Dec 29, 1943 [Jan 25, 1944 PM] [Apr 24, 1945 PM] Feb 11, 1946 Jul 18, 1946 Sep 9, 1946 Sep 23, 1946 May 8, 1947 Aug 15, 1947 Jun 16, 1948 [1948] [Aug 8, 1950 PM] [Aug 11, 1950 PM] [Apr 6, 1956 PM] Oct 29, 1956
Roman Bronze Corporation Nov 30, 1934 Jul 17, 1946 Sep 19, 1946 Sep 23, 1946
Romero, Pepe *[circa 1955] Nov 5, 1956 [circa Dec 1956]
Rona, Lily Dec 30, 1955
Roosevelt, Theodore, President of the U.S. (1858-1919) -- staff Feb 12, 1902 See also Correspondence of others: Weschler, Hulda Mayer
Rosenberg, Harold *Feb 9, 1960 Feb 14, 1960
Ross, Hugh [Feb 1937]
Roth, Benjamin *Jun 4, 1937
Rowan, Eward B. Jan 29, 1936 *Jan 6 [1938] Mar 29, 1938 May 2, 1938 *May 5, 1938 Jun 16, 1938 Jun 30, 1938 Jul 5, 1938 *Jul 9, 1938 Jul 14, 1938 Aug 1, 1938 *Sep 14, 1938 Oct 5, 1938 Oct 10, 1938 *Oct 13, 1938 Oct 15, 1938 Oct 21, 1938 *Nov 1, 1938 *Nov 28,1938 Dec 6, 1938 *Dec 8, 1938 *[circa 1938] *[circa 1938] *Feb 6, 1939 Jun 2, 1939 *Jun 22, 1939 Jun 26, 1939 Mar 13, 1940 *[circa Mar 15, 1940] Nov 1, 1941
Rudd, Deforest Porter Jan 13, 1938
Rudy, Charles Nov 29, 1950
San Francisco Museum of Art Mar 24, 1938 Jun 1, 1938 *Jul 14, 1940 Jul 18, 1940 Sep 28, 1941 Oct 20, 1941 Nov 28, 1941 Jan 5, 1942 *Jan 12, 1942 Jan 16, 1942 Feb 3, 1942 Apr 22, 1942
Sarah Lawrence College *Apr 21, 1949 Apr 25, 1949
Schaffer, Rose Dec 23, 1952 Feb 28 [1953 PM] Mar 28, 1953
Schlesing, Heiner Jun 5, 1933 Dec 3, 1933 Jan 1, 1935 [circa 1935] Mar 15, 1940 Jul 2, 1947 Aug 12, 1948
Schlick, Fredrick Jun 24, 1931 May 25, 1935 Jun 30, 1940 Jul 14, 1941 Aug 14 [1941 PM] Aug 26, 1941 Nov 24 [1943 PM] Feb 12, 1945 Jun 19, 1949 Dec 16, 1949 May 15, 1950 May 22, 1950 Jul 16, 1950 Apr 19, 1952 [circa 1952] [circa 1952 [circa 1952 Jun 16, 1942 *Jun 26, 1942 *Apr 27 [1942 PM] *Jan 23, 1957
Schlick, Robert Oct 4, 1947
Schwarz, Karl Feb 1, 1952
Sculptor's Guild Dec 3, 1941 *[circa 1942] Sep 17, 1943 [May 3, 1946 PM] Jul 23, 1946 [1946] [circa May 9, 1947] Jun 6 [1947] Jan 4, 1948 Jan 12, 1948 Oct 26, 1948 Mar 13, 1950 Mar 13 [circa 1950] [Nov 7, 1950 PM] [Nov 20, 1950 PM] Mar 16, 1951 Mar 16, 1951 Oct 1, 1951 Nov 30, 1951 [Dec 23, 1951 PM] [1951] Jan 22, 1952 Jan 27, 1952 Sep 11, 1952 Sep 2, 1955 Apr 20, 1956 Aug 9, 1957 [circa 1957] [Mar 9, 1960 PM] n.d.
Sculpture in Replica Apr 7, 1952 *Apr 30, 1952 Oct 19, 1952 *Nov 24 [1952] Feb 19, 1953 Mar 14, 1953
Selznick, David O. Aug [circa 1925]
Shaman & Schlick Publishers, Inc. Feb 4, 1946 Feb 14, 1946 *Mar 15, 1946
Shire, Mildred [Feb 1937]
Skidelsky, Sibilla Jan 15, 1941 *Jan 16, 1941
Slochower, Harry [Feb 19371
Slocum, Rosalie Oct 31, 1955 Nov 15, 1955
Smith, Chard Powers Mar 13, 1937 [circa 1947]
Smith, Warren Allen Nov 11, 1955 *Nov 23, 1955 Nov 26, 1955 *Dec 16, 1955 Feb 24, 1956 Apr 23, 1956 *May 4, 1956 Jul 21, 1956 Aug 21, 1956 Nov 10, 1956 [circa 1956] May 13, 1957 Oct 6, 1957 Feb 19, 1958
Society of Independent Artists, Inc. Mar 5, 1941